https://www.americancentury.com/en/legal/privacy.html

Cookie Settings
It's a Matter of Privacy-Yours
Trust is the foundation of any solid relationship. At American Century Investments®, trust takes on even greater importance because you are entrusting your money to our care. We understand you are also entrusting us with your goals and plans for your financial future. We take that seriously and work hard to do the right thing. We apply this same integrity to protecting your privacy.
Review our Privacy Notice  to understand how we protect your personal information.
Learn more about the information we gather online and how you can protect yourself.
California Residents
Our Use of Web Analytics
Our Use of Cookies and Clear Gifs
Secure Online Account Access
Web Browser Requirements
Preventing Online Fraud
Contacting American Century Investments
Notification of Changes
California Residents
California law provides additional privacy rights to California residents. Review our California Privacy Notice to understand these rights and how California residents can exercise them.
Our Use of Web Analytics
We use third party tools to track the usage of our website. Tracking information does not include any personally identifiable information. Cookies, which are set on behalf of American Century Investments, report this data so we can better understand our users and to improve our site. American Century Investments does not honor "do not track" requests. However, we will not use targeting cookies or similar tools that transmit your data to third parties for advertising purposes unless we receive your consent first.
Our Use of Cookies & Clear Gifs
If you conduct business with American Century Investments online, you may notice our use of Internet cookies. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser and customize your experience on our website and help us better understand how our investors use our website.
What Is a Cookie?
A cookie is a small piece of alphanumeric information placed on your computer by the website you are visiting. It allows the website to remember or recognize your computer during subsequent visits. Although websites use cookies for different purposes, one important function is to allow a site to personalize your experience. For example, cookies help us better understand how account owners use our website so we can improve your online experience. Once you are logged in, cookies maintain your security as you move from page to page within the site.
What Types of Cookies Do Websites Put on My Computer?
Temporary: Cookies that are stored on your computer only during your browsing session, and are automatically deleted from your computer when you close your browser. No information is collected from your computer.
Persistent: Cookies that are stored on your computer and are not deleted when you close your browser. Permanent cookies retain your preferences for a particular website, allowing those preferences to remain for future browsing sessions. No information is collected from your computer.
How Does American Century Investments Use Cookies?
We use cookies to facilitate your use of our website. These cookies do not collect or contain any personally identifiable information. Examples of how we use cookies include:
Temporary Cookies
All Secure Pages: American Century Investments and Pershing, our clearing agent for brokerage customers, use temporary cookies on all secure pages. These cookies store a session ID that is not personally identifiable to you, allowing you to move from page to page without having to log in repeatedly.
Persistent Cookies
All Pages: These cookies are set by Adobe Analytics, Google Analytics and/or Eloqua to help us analyze online behavior and identify areas of the site where users are having difficulty completing a task. We use this information to help build a better website.
Brokerage Model Portfolio: This cookie is set by Pershing to collect browser information for use with their Model Portfolio service. It allows you to access your Model Portfolio during subsequent visits.
Home Page: This cookie is set by American Century Investments and allows customers to bypass the corporate homepage when they indicate a preference for a section of the site they would like to view on future visits.
What Is a Clear Gif and How Are They Used?
A clear gif, also known as a Web Beacon, is similar in function to cookies. It is a tiny graphic with a unique identifier that is invisible on the page and much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs track online web movements of our users and inform us what content is effective. Clear gifs do not transmit users' personal information.
In addition, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know when they have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to understand the effectiveness of our communications and tailor future emails to meet user needs.
Users may choose to opt-out of these emails through the following link.
Unsubscribe from Email for Individual Investors
Secure Online Account Access
Web Security & You
Protecting your privacy and security is a shared responsibility. We affirm our commitment to safeguard your personal information; however, it is imperative that you protect your Password to prevent unauthorized access to your accounts. For this reason, we strongly suggest that you do not share your Password with anyone. If you do choose to give it to someone, such as a so-called "financial aggregator" that combines information about you from multiple sources over the Internet, you do so at your own risk. We cannot be responsible for any losses you may incur as a result.
Mutual Fund & Brokerage Customers
Registration is the process of creating a unique User Name, Password, and enrolling in multifactor authentication via text message (SMS), voice call or authenticator application. These steps are required to log in and securely access your American Century Investments accounts and other services. Any personal or financial information you provide during the Registration process is kept confidential, as stated in this Privacy and Security Policy.
Forgotten Passwords or Locked Accounts
Unlock your accounts securely online by selecting the forgot user name link below the User Name entry field at the top of most pages on americancentury.com, and following the prompts.
Web Browser Requirements
We require users to access their accounts online with Mozilla Firefox , Microsoft Internet Explorer , Google Chrome  or Apple Safari . These browsers use 128-bit encryption and Transport Layer Security 1.2 (TLS 1.2). This technology helps enable the security of your online sessions.
If for any reason your session is no longer secure, you will be disconnected from online account access.
If a session is secure, it means that it is encrypted. Every secure page on American Century Investments website has been secured with a digital certificate by Symantec. We use 128-bit encryption, TLS 1.2, and proprietary encryption algorithms to secure your connection when you are accessing your account online. American Century Investments supports 128-bit encryption to provide you with secure access to your account information. If your browser does not support 128-bit encryption or TLS 1.2, we recommend that you upgrade your browser to a newer version. Please access the Mozilla Firefox , Microsoft Internet Explorer , Google Chrome  or Apple Safari  websites to upgrade your browser to the current version.
Browser Security Indicators
Use the information below to help you determine the security features within your browser.
Non-Secure Connection
All Browsers: No Lock indicates a non-secure connection
Secure Connection
Mozilla Firefox
Microsoft Internet Explorer  *
Google Chrome
Apple Safari
* See Microsoft's Lifecycle Support policy for Internet Explorer  for more information about supported version.
To view the encryption certificate, click on the image of the closed lock or globe in the top bar of your browser window. A small frame displaying site security information will appear.
This site may contain links to other sites. American Century Investments is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Preventing Online Fraud
Online fraud comes in many forms, such as phishing or malware (malicious software), and uses phony emails, websites and other software to trick you into providing your personal information. Learn how you can prevent online fraud.
Contacting American Century Investments
American Century Investments believes that your privacy should be respected. We appreciate and take seriously your trust in us and our ability to safeguard your personal information. For more information about our privacy commitment please contact one of our Investment Consultants at 1-800-345-2021 or visit our Contact Us page.
If you would like to opt out of future marketing mailings, you may:
Mail your request to:
Chief Privacy Officer
American Century Investments
PO Box 419200
Kansas City, MO 64141-6200
Call 1-800-345-2021
Monday through Friday, 8 a.m. to 6 p.m. Central time
Unsubscribe from Email for Individual Investors
Notification of Changes
We will post any changes to this privacy statement so users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any we disclose it. If, however, we are going to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our website for 30 days prior to implementing the change.
Effective Date of this Policy
January 1, 2020
Explore More
Security Center
Site Help
